<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Posts on Aaron Reding</title>
		<link>https://aaronreding.net/posts/</link>
		<description>Recent content in Posts on Aaron Reding</description>
		<generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
		<language>en-us</language>
		<copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		<atom:link href="https://aaronreding.net/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
		<item>
			<title>BUGS to PyMC</title>
			<link>https://aaronreding.net/posts/bugstopymc/</link>
			<pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			
			<guid>https://aaronreding.net/posts/bugstopymc/</guid>
			<description>Redoing an older Bayesian Statistics course with more modern tools I&amp;rsquo;m working on translating the examples from Professor Vidakovic&amp;rsquo;s Bayesian Statistics course at Georgia Tech from MATLAB and OpenBUGS to Python (using libraries PyMC3 and pgmpy). As a former student and current TA, by far the number one complaint I&amp;rsquo;ve heard about the course is that OpenBUGS is outdated and a waste of time to learn. I chose PyMC because among the newer Probabilistic Programming Languages it seems the easiest to learn, especially since I&amp;rsquo;m most familiar with Python.</description>
			<content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="redoing-an-older-bayesian-statistics-course-with-more-modern-tools">Redoing an older Bayesian Statistics course with more modern tools</h2>
<p>I&rsquo;m working on translating the examples from Professor Vidakovic&rsquo;s Bayesian Statistics course at Georgia Tech from MATLAB and OpenBUGS to Python (using libraries PyMC3 and pgmpy). As a former student and current TA, by far the number one complaint I&rsquo;ve heard about the course is that OpenBUGS is outdated and a waste of time to learn. I chose PyMC because among the newer <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Probabilistic_programming#List_of_probabilistic_programming_languages">Probabilistic Programming Languages</a> it seems the easiest to learn, especially since I&rsquo;m most familiar with Python.</p>
<p>The project can be found <a href="https://areding.github.io/6420-pymc/">here</a>. It&rsquo;s made with <a href="https://jupyterbook.org/">Jupyter book</a>, and makes use of PyMC 3, <a href="https://github.com/pymc-devs/pymc">PyMC 4</a>, <a href="https://numpy.org/">NumPy</a>, <a href="https://arviz-devs.github.io/arviz/">Arviz</a>, and <a href="https://pgmpy.org/">pgmpy</a>.</p>
<h2 id="todo">Todo:</h2>
<ul>
<li><input checked="" disabled="" type="checkbox"> Mad scramble to get enough examples relating to each homework in the Spring 2022 semester.</li>
<li><input disabled="" type="checkbox"> Finish adding all examples from the original course.</li>
<li><input disabled="" type="checkbox"> Convert the remaining PyMC 3 examples to PyMC 4.</li>
<li><input disabled="" type="checkbox"> Reorganize the table of contents and add tags for easier navigation.</li>
<li><input disabled="" type="checkbox"> Rename each example to be a little more descriptive.</li>
<li><input disabled="" type="checkbox"> Fix the look of the site:
<ul>
<li><input disabled="" type="checkbox"> Resize markdown tables.</li>
<li><input disabled="" type="checkbox"> Dark mode option?</li>
<li><input disabled="" type="checkbox"> Make syntax highlighting better-looking.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li><input disabled="" type="checkbox"> Add more content relating to MCMC algorithms. Especially since the course only covers Metropolis and Gibbs but PyMC uses Hamiltonian/NUTS.</li>
<li><input disabled="" type="checkbox"> Add FAQ.</li>
<li><input disabled="" type="checkbox"> Add a centralized references page and/or more official references to each page (right now it&rsquo;s just in-line links).</li>
<li><input disabled="" type="checkbox"> Improve visualizations.</li>
<li><input disabled="" type="checkbox"> More content relating to prior elicitation.</li>
<li><input disabled="" type="checkbox"> More content relating to model validation.</li>
</ul>
]]></content>
		</item>
		
		<item>
			<title>Tianjin soup-filled dumplings</title>
			<link>https://aaronreding.net/posts/tianjindumplings/</link>
			<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			
			<guid>https://aaronreding.net/posts/tianjindumplings/</guid>
			<description>For quite a while after I first came to China, I was scared to go to new restaurants alone and order in Chinese. I walked everywhere, and we live on a pretty huge hill, so I would occasionally get hungry enough to overcome my fear of interaction. (I lost about 10 pounds during this period. Unfortunately, as my Chinese got better, my weight went back up.) This post is about</description>
			<content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>For quite a while after I first came to China, I was scared to go to new restaurants alone and order in Chinese. I walked everywhere, and we live on a pretty huge hill, so I would occasionally get hungry enough to overcome my fear of interaction. (I lost about 10 pounds during this period. Unfortunately, as my Chinese got better, my weight went back up.)</p>
<p>This post is about the menu at Tianjin Soup Dumplings, a tiny restaurant near my elementary school. My interactions with the owner at first were limited to something like:</p>
<blockquote>
<p>”你好，可以买一笼包子和一个鸡蛋？” (Hello, can I buy a basket of buns and an egg?)<br>
“九快。” (9 yuan.)<br>
“谢谢。” (Thanks.) <br>
“不用谢。” (No need for thanks.)</p>
</blockquote>
<figure><img src="/images/tianjinbaozi.jpg"
         alt="A basket of baozi."/><figcaption>
            <p>一笼包子</p>
        </figcaption>
</figure>

<p>One time, feeling adventurous, I tried to order soup buns (sometimes known as soup dumplings in English), but I thought they were called 小笼包 (xiǎo lóng bāo, little basket buns). 2 minutes later I received my usual order of non-soup buns. Now that I&rsquo;m translating this menu, I see why. Here they call them 汤包 (tāng bāo, literally, soup buns). Also my pronunciation was probably terrible. I&rsquo;ll try ordering 汤包 next time and see what happens.</p>
<p>Anyways, to improve my vocabulary and maybe help out other people heading to China, I&rsquo;m planning on doing a series of posts translating menus at places I&rsquo;ve been to in China. I won&rsquo;t be able to post pictures of all the food, since I can&rsquo;t order everything, but you can image-search the Chinese names  for most items and see what they look like.</p>
<p>Here&rsquo;s the menu (notice the green WeChat Pay and blue AliPay QR codes):</p>
<figure><img src="/images/tianjintangbaomenu.jpg"
         alt="Tianjin Tangbao menu."/><figcaption>
            <p>天津灌汤菜单</p>
        </figcaption>
</figure>

<p>Here&rsquo;s my translation:</p>
<table>
<thead>
<tr>
<th>天津灌汤包价目表</th>
<th style="text-align:left"></th>
</tr>
</thead>
<tbody>
<tr>
<td>Tiānjīn guàn tāng bāo jiàmù biǎo (Tianjin soup-filled dumplings price list)</td>
<td style="text-align:left"></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>生煎包</td>
<td style="text-align:left">10元10个</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>shēng jiān bāo (pan-fried buns)</td>
<td style="text-align:left">10 yuán 10 gè (10 for ¥10)</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>锅铁饺</td>
<td style="text-align:left">10元10个</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>guō tiě jiǎo (pan-fried dumplings)</td>
<td style="text-align:left">10 yuán 10 gè (10 for ¥10)</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>鸡汁灌汤包</td>
<td style="text-align:left">8元/笼</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>jī zhī guàn tāng bāo (chicken juice soup-filled dumplings)</td>
<td style="text-align:left">8 yuán/lóng (¥8/basket)</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>鲜肉包</td>
<td style="text-align:left">7元/笼</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>xiān ròu bāo (fresh meat buns)</td>
<td style="text-align:left">7 yuán/lóng (¥7/basket)</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>香菇包</td>
<td style="text-align:left">7元/笼</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>xiānggū bāo (fragrant mushroom buns)</td>
<td style="text-align:left">7 yuán/lóng (¥7/basket)</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>豆沙包</td>
<td style="text-align:left">7元/笼</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>dòushā bāo (red bean paste buns)</td>
<td style="text-align:left">7 yuán/lóng (¥7/basket)</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>肉丁烧麦</td>
<td style="text-align:left">7元/笼</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>ròu dīng shāomài (sliced meat rice dumplings)</td>
<td style="text-align:left">7 yuán/lóng (¥7/basket)</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>鲜肉蒸饺</td>
<td style="text-align:left">7元/笼</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>xiān ròu zhēng jiǎo (fresh meat steamed dumplings)</td>
<td style="text-align:left">7 yuán/lóng (¥7/basket)</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>韭菜鸡蛋蒸饺</td>
<td style="text-align:left">7元/笼</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>jiǔcài jīdàn zhēng jiǎo (chive and chicken egg steamed dumplings)</td>
<td style="text-align:left">7 yuán/lóng (¥7/basket)</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>皮蛋瘦肉粥</td>
<td style="text-align:left">5元/碗</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>pídàn shòu ròu zhōu (century egg and lean meat congee)</td>
<td style="text-align:left">5 yuán/wǎn (¥5/bowl)</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>黑米粥</td>
<td style="text-align:left">3元/碗</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>hēi mǐ zhōu (black rice congee)</td>
<td style="text-align:left">3 yuán/wǎn (¥3/bowl)</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>南瓜粥</td>
<td style="text-align:left">3元/碗</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>nánguā zhōu (pumpkin congee)</td>
<td style="text-align:left">3 yuán/wǎn (¥3/bowl)</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>绿豆粥</td>
<td style="text-align:left">3元/碗</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>lǜdòu zhōu (mung bean congee)</td>
<td style="text-align:left">3 yuán/wǎn (¥3/bowl)</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>大米稀饭</td>
<td style="text-align:left">2元/碗</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>dàmǐ xīfan (rice congee)</td>
<td style="text-align:left">2 yuán/wǎn (¥2/bowl)</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>九阳豆浆</td>
<td style="text-align:left">3元/杯</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>jiǔ yáng dòujiāng (nine sun soy milk)</td>
<td style="text-align:left">3 yuán/bēi (¥3/cup)</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>咸鸭蛋</td>
<td style="text-align:left">2元/个</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>xián yādàn (salty duck eggs)</td>
<td style="text-align:left">2 yuán/gè (¥2 each)</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>五香茶叶蛋</td>
<td style="text-align:left">2元/个</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>wǔxiāng cháyè dàn (five-spice tea leaf eggs)</td>
<td style="text-align:left">2 yuán/gè (¥2 each)</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>煮水饺</td>
<td style="text-align:left">10元/碗</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>zhǔ shuǐjiǎo (boiled dumplings)</td>
<td style="text-align:left">10 yuán/wǎn (¥10/bowl)</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>煮馄饨</td>
<td style="text-align:left">7元/碗</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>zhǔ húntún (boiled wontons)</td>
<td style="text-align:left">7 yuán/wǎn (¥7/bowl)</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
<h3 id="translation-notes">Translation notes</h3>
<h3 id="prices">Prices</h3>
<p>They&rsquo;re cheap. Any one of those ¥7 ($1) baskets will fill you up. Notice there are 4 different measure words for the prices: 个 (gè, each), 笼 (lóng, basket), 碗 (wǎn, bowl), and 杯 (bēi, cup).</p>
<h3 id="pan-fried">Pan-fried</h3>
<ul>
<li>
<h4 id="生煎包-shēng-jiān-bāo">生煎包 shēng jiān bāo</h4>
</li>
<li>
<h4 id="锅铁饺-guō-tiě-jiǎo">锅铁饺 guō tiě jiǎo</h4>
<p>I&rsquo;m not sure why one of these is 锅铁 and one is 生煎, but they&rsquo;re pretty straightforward. They&rsquo;re both pan-fried versions of either 饺子 (jiǎozi, dumplings) or 包子 (bāozi, buns).</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="steamer-baskets">Steamer baskets</h3>
<ul>
<li>
<h4 id="鸡汁灌汤包-jī-zhī-guàn-tāng-bāo">鸡汁灌汤包 jī zhī guàn tāng bāo</h4>
<p>Chicken juice is the literal translation of 鸡汁. Maybe chicken broth would be more accurate. But really, who needs two words for juice and broth. Maybe English should just settle on one.</p>
</li>
<li>
<h4 id="鲜肉包-xiān-ròu-bāo">鲜肉包 xiān ròu bāo</h4>
<p>Fresh pork meat buns. Notice that pork isn&rsquo;t actually specified here, just 肉 or meat. But you can probably assume it&rsquo;s pork when that happens. This is what I was ordering when I only knew how to order one thing. They&rsquo;re delicious - full-size baozi usually have too much steamed bread for me.</p>
</li>
<li>
<h4 id="香菇包-xiānggū-bāo">香菇包 xiānggū bāo</h4>
<p>Same as above, but filled with &ldquo;fragrant mushrooms.&rdquo; Haven&rsquo;t tried these yet.</p>
</li>
<li>
<h4 id="豆沙包-dòushā-bāo">豆沙包 dòushā bāo</h4>
<p>Red bean buns, lightly sweetened. I don&rsquo;t think I&rsquo;ve ordered them here, but if you know what you&rsquo;re getting in to they&rsquo;re pretty good. If you&rsquo;re expecting something savory, then you will be unhappy.</p>
</li>
<li>
<h4 id="肉丁烧麦-ròu-dīng-shāomài">肉丁烧麦 ròu dīng shāomài</h4>
<p>These shaomai are dumpling skin, wrapped around pork-fried rice, with the top part open. I&rsquo;ve had them a few times here. They&rsquo;re good, but a lot of carbs if that&rsquo;s all you&rsquo;re eating. They&rsquo;re in the back of the image below.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<figure><img src="/images/tangbaocongeeshaomai.jpg"
         alt="Congee, eggs, buns."/><figcaption>
            <p>粥， 鸡蛋，包子</p>
        </figcaption>
</figure>

<p>From left to right: congee (稀饭), a salty duck egg, soup buns, and a tea egg. Those little white roots are 折耳根 (zhé ěrgēn, fish mint roots), a Guiyang specialty. Also pictured: I am a horribly messy eater.</p>
<ul>
<li>
<h4 id="鲜肉蒸饺-xiān-ròu-zhēng-jiǎo">鲜肉蒸饺 xiān ròu zhēng jiǎo</h4>
</li>
<li>
<h4 id="韭菜鸡蛋蒸饺-jiǔcài-jīdàn-zhēng-jiǎo">韭菜鸡蛋蒸饺 jiǔcài jīdàn zhēng jiǎo</h4>
<p>These are fresh meat steamed dumplings and chive and chicken egg steamed dumplings. I haven&rsquo;t tried either here yet.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="congee">Congee</h3>
<ul>
<li>
<h4 id="皮蛋瘦肉粥-pídàn-shòu-ròu-zhōu">皮蛋瘦肉粥 pídàn shòu ròu zhōu</h4>
<p><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Century_egg">Century egg</a> and lean meat congee. Century eggs are those translucent black and green preserved duck eggs. Definitely an acquired taste. One which I have acquired.</p>
</li>
<li>
<h4 id="黑米粥-hēi-mǐ-zhōu">黑米粥 hēi mǐ zhōu</h4>
</li>
<li>
<h4 id="南瓜粥-nánguā-zhōu">南瓜粥 nánguā zhōu</h4>
</li>
<li>
<h4 id="绿豆粥-lǜdòu-zhōu">绿豆粥 lǜdòu zhōu</h4>
<p>Black rice, pumpkin, and mung bean congee.</p>
</li>
<li>
<h4 id="大米稀饭-dàmǐ-xīfan">大米稀饭 dàmǐ xīfan</h4>
<p>This is plain congee. I&rsquo;m not sure exactly what the difference between 粥 and 稀饭 is. It depends on who I ask. Maybe 稀饭 is thinner, or maybe 粥 is a more general term (so it can be other grains besides rice), or both.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="sides">Sides</h3>
<ul>
<li>
<h4 id="九阳豆浆-jiǔ-yáng-dòujiāng">九阳豆浆 jiǔ yáng dòujiāng</h4>
<p>Hot, sweetened soy milk.</p>
</li>
<li>
<h4 id="咸鸭蛋-xián-yādàn-salty-duck-eggs">咸鸭蛋 xián yādàn (salty duck eggs)</h4>
<p>They aren&rsquo;t kidding about the salty part. These are great, but you have to break them up and eat a little bit at a time, maybe mixed with congee. Pictured above.</p>
</li>
<li>
<h4 id="五香茶叶蛋-wǔxiāng-cháyè-dàn">五香茶叶蛋 wǔxiāng cháyè dàn</h4>
<p>AKA tea eggs. Sometimes I see these listed as 卤鸡蛋 (lǔ jīdàn, braised eggs). Half of one pictured above.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="boiled">Boiled</h3>
<ul>
<li>
<h4 id="煮水饺-zhǔ-shuǐjiǎo">煮水饺 zhǔ shuǐjiǎo</h4>
</li>
<li>
<h4 id="煮馄饨-zhǔ-húntún">煮馄饨 zhǔ húntún</h4>
<p>Boiled dumplings or wontons, served in a bowl with the water they were boiled in.</p>
</li>
</ul>
]]></content>
		</item>
		
		<item>
			<title>Group essays in small classes</title>
			<link>https://aaronreding.net/posts/groupessays/</link>
			<pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			
			<guid>https://aaronreding.net/posts/groupessays/</guid>
			<description>One of my favorite exercises for small classes of intermediate students is the group essay. When I first started teaching, we would always write individual essays, as called for in the provided lesson plan. But that resulted in long periods of quiet, which isn’t great for an oral English class.
So I asked the students to take turns coming up with a sentence while I transcribed them. The result is usually a much more engaged class.</description>
			<content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>One of my favorite exercises for small classes of intermediate students is the group essay. When I first started teaching, we would always write individual essays, as called for in the provided lesson plan. But that resulted in long periods of quiet, which isn’t great for an oral English class.</p>
<p>So I asked the students to take turns coming up with a sentence while I transcribed them. The result is usually a much more engaged class. Even the shyer students participate.</p>
<p>I don’t limit what they can write for the most part, and I use the opportunity to teach some minor grammar points appropriate for their level. My goal isn’t to make the grammar or writing perfect, just to reinforce what they’ve learned and get them to use language creatively.</p>
<p>The main reason I want to post this is to save some of these classics for posterity.</p>
<h2 id="examples">Examples</h2>
<p>This first essay prompt was something like this: you’re walking on a beach, and see a tree with a box. Describe what you see, what’s in the box, and what you do after.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>I walked slowly along the beach. I saw many trees. I saw many beautiful girls. It&rsquo;s very exciting.</p>
<p>I saw a tree. It was very tall. I climbed to the top, and I heard many beautiful songs. They are from the sea. Suddenly, I saw a box on the tree. I take the box. It&rsquo;s black and small. I open the box, and find something special.</p>
<p>Inside the box, there is an old man&rsquo;s diary. Inside the diary, there is a treasure map. The treasure map says to walk along the beach and inside the second tree, under the tree, you can find many things that you want. I dug a hole under the second tree. I found a paper.</p>
<p>On the paper, there is a saying, &ldquo;You must try your best to face any danger.&rdquo; I swam into the sea and died.</p>
<p>THE END</p>
</blockquote>
<hr>
<p>The prompt for this next one was “Where will your next vacation be? Will you stay in a hotel or with friends? What will you do?”</p>
<blockquote>
<p>We are going to America this vacation. First, we will find a bad hotel for 10 yuan. Then we will eat food for 5 yuan. We will sell our luggage and clothes. We will get a lot of money, but then, we will be arrested for not having any clothes. And go to jail.</p>
<p>We can live in the jail. We have food, new clothes, and a place to sleep. It is very free. It&rsquo;s very comfortable. We can make a lot of friends, although they are not very friendly. Then we can escape from the jail and kill people. Then we can&rsquo;t use the money.</p>
<p>Then, we will be deported to China. And we didn&rsquo;t spend any money on the plane ticket home. And this trip, we only spent 15 yuan, and the money for the plane ticket there. We are very frugal.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>It is very free.</p>
<hr>
<p>Write a letter to your friend describing your vacation.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Hi Peter,</p>
<p>How are you? I miss you very much. I love you.</p>
<p>Last weekend, I went to Vietnam with my friends. We visited some interesting places such as the sea. We went to the sea and ate fresh seafood. And we bought some interesting things. We went to the biggest restaurant in Vietnam. We ate braised red-crown crane, steamed giant panda, and roast koala. Then the policeman came and arrested us because we ate these protected animals. Then we went to the police station. The bed at the police station was very comfortable. We ate some delicious food, such as more braised red-crown crane.</p>
<p>Then the policemen kicked us. We were hurt. Then we went to the hospital. The doctor told me my arm was broken. Then I took a break. The next day, I felt very good so I hung out with my friends, and we had a big meal. I lost my passport, so I can&rsquo;t come back to China. Help me, please!</p>
<p>My phone number is 1582102384. My email is <a href="mailto:32145@qq.com">32145@qq.com</a>. You can follow me on Weibo. I will broadcast the escape.</p>
<p>Best wishes,</p>
<p>Sandwich, Lisa, Denver</p>
</blockquote>
<p>I think they had just learned &ldquo;such as.&rdquo;</p>
<hr>
<p>Here&rsquo;s another variation on the beach dream essay.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>I go along the beach and there are bodies everywhere. I walk on a brain. The sky was very dark. There is an old woman, and I can see her eyes. She catches me, and asks me, &ldquo;Do you need insurance?&rdquo; I run away and I shout to her, &ldquo;No, I don&rsquo;t! You must be crazy!&rdquo;</p>
<p>I go along again. I can see many fish on the beach. They are all dead. Suddenly, I see a yellow box, and a pink star. They catch me. I ask them, &ldquo;Who are you?&rdquo; The yellow box answers, &ldquo;I&rsquo;m SpongeBob.&rdquo; The pink star answers, &ldquo;I&rsquo;m Patrick.&rdquo;</p>
<p>Then I cook them for dinner. Really delicious. Then I see a tree. There are many dead bodies hanging on the branches. They all say, &ldquo;Do you need insurance?&rdquo; They are all chasing me. I climb up a tree. I stay there for five days. Suddenly, an old man killed the zombies. He lets me say, &ldquo;Shazam!&rdquo; And I say no!</p>
<p>The old man is very angry. He asks, &ldquo;Why?&rdquo; And I answer, &ldquo;Because I&rsquo;m Batman.&rdquo; The old man is very surprised. The old man asks, &ldquo;Do you need insurance?&rdquo; In the end, I say, &ldquo;Expecto Patronum!&rdquo; And the world has peace.</p>
<p>​		THE END</p>
</blockquote>
]]></content>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
